True Beauty
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
The True Beauty Team @ Viki
True Beauty
Episode 14
Hey. I heard that Im Ju Gyeong came to school bare-faced.
But do you think it's true she's dating Lee Su Ho?
Seeing her bare face earlier, it looked a lot worse than the picture.
He probably broke up after seeing her bare face. How can you date someone with that face?
Isn't Lee Su Ho out these days, too? His dad is totally out.
Maybe he's lost it and is dating anybody.
Wow, that's harsh.
Hey, let's go.
Hey, what's this? Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, you guys! Take back what you just said.
Im Ju Gyeong?
Walking around bare-faced, you must be crazy.
That's right, I'm dating Lee Su Ho.
Lee Su Ho is my boyfriend!
Happy? Does that resolve your curiosity?
- I think she's crazy.
- I think you're right.
He doesn't discriminate against people for their looks.
And he likes me as who I am no matter how I look.
So he's so much better than you guys with ruined personalities.
So don't gossip about him to drag him down just because we're dating,
and come and talk to me personally from now on.
I will counter every single thing, got it?
And rather than evaluating people's looks, go and study during that time!
Get out of my way!
It must be true.
I'm so jealous.
♫ Love so fine ♫
♫ Come closer, approach me ♫
♫ Lean in my arms ♫
♫ Always in my heart. I think I’m in love with you ♫
♫ Love so fine ♫
♫ You’re so right ♫
♫ Your lovely look ♫
Let's go.
♫ I'm going to spend all the time with you ♫
♫ I don't want to let go of even a moment ♫
♫ Stay with me like this ♫
Hi, what should we go eat today?
- Tteokbooki. There was a good place.
- Really?
Lover? I definitely don't have one.
Wow, your car is nice. Your job must be going well.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah.
Shall I give it to you?
You're cute.
You should be my grapefruit from now on.
I'm the grapefruit!
You scared me.
I want to eat some grapefruit.
It's because I like grapefruits.
- They really must be dating.
- Ah, I envy her.
It looks like our secret dating is over now.
Yeah. Today, I came out with my bare face and my dating life.
Are you okay?
No. It feels like my heart became as small as a bean.
Then you should have come like how you normally do.
Last time, Go Woon told me this.
That if I dislike my face just because people are cursing at me,
then I'm acknowledging that I'm ugly.
So from now on, I'm only going to listen to those who like me.
The words that people who don't know me well say easily...
I won't bother with them.
I won't run or hide anymore.
So that's why I came bare-faced.
You're all grown up, Im Ju Gyeong.
Yeah, Mom. Noona is fine.
God Su Ho is also next to her.
What? God Su Ho?
- Don't worry.
- There aren't any kids who are bullying her?
I don't have to charge in, do I?
Okay.
Did he say Ju Gyeong is okay?
Seems like she's doing fine from what he's saying,
but we don't know how she's really feeling.
She'll be all right. Whose daughter is she?
Why did you come here?
Leave!
Leave! Leave!
Leave?  U-U-Us?
Instead of shaking the heart of someone who's not doing anything! Leave! Leave!
What kind of crazy person?
Teacher Han?
T-Teacher?
Hello.
This is a no-parking zone.
But because you parked here, I was upset.
Goodbye.
Why did he get so riled over parking?
Does he have some anger management disorder?
No. A cute control disorder.
- Huh? What the...?
- Oh, wow!
- Whoa!
- Wow, hurray!
What is going on?  What's this?
- Wow.
- This is awesome!
Ah, seriously.
I'm seriously so jealous.
Ju Gyeong, I worried a lot.
But you were kind of cool back there.
[- Hye Min]
Hello.
- Time for dismissal, kids.
- You mean morning announcement.
Of course.
The student who isn't a part of our class should leave now.
Mr. Han, that's Im Ju Gyeong.
She probably is.
- Ju Gyeong?
- Yes?
You're Ju Gyeong?
- Yes.
- Ju Gyeong...
Ju Gyeong, welcome back.
Never mind.
I... Ju Gyeong... I... to Ju Gyeong...You...
I worried a lot about Ju Gyeong.
Is Teacher crying?
Don't cry.
Is he really crying?
Guys, I'm sorry.
Ju Gyeong has finally returned!
Don't cry!
Don't cry! Don't cry!
I'm really sorry.
Ju Gyeong— That's it!
What the...?
How could you think about coming here looking like that?
What'd you say?
It's not like you're putting on a show for the whole school.
You wanted to receive attention this way?
It looks like since Lee Su Ho is next to you, you gained courage that was nonexistent before.
Hey, Kang Su Jin!
- You really...!
- Su Ah...
Kang Su Jin, you're seriously the worst.
It wouldn't have been enough for you to kneel before Ju Gyeong and beg, but what'd you say?
- Have you said everything?
- Why do I have to beg before her?
You're the one who spread Ju Gyeong's video on the bulletin board!
- Someone stop him.
- Where are they going?
- Should I stop him?
- What's wrong with him?
- Hey, where are you going?
Im Ju Gyeong... You think you destroyed her, don't you?
The one who's been destroyed is you.
That's right. At first, I tried to understand you.
That maybe you did it impulsively out of jealousy because you liked Lee Su Ho.
If so, then at least you would be regretting it by now.
Because Ju Gyeong hasn't been coming to school,
that you would, although late, feel sorry and worry about her.
That's what I thought.
So... I was waiting for you to apologize to her first.
But... you were this kind of person?
Yeah, turns out I am this type of person.
Su Ah!
Kang Su Jin, for what reason are you going this far to ruin everything?
Is something going on at home? Is it because of your dad?
What's it to you?
Because no matter how much I think about it, I'm not getting an answer.
You weren't originally this type of person.
Is this really what you wanted?
- Yeah.
- I know it's not. I also know you're going to regret it.
But even if it's now, you should go and apologize to Ju Gyeong.
- Apologize and—
- Don't concern yourself.
Su Ah!
Wait a moment Su Ah!
- I'm sorry.
- Let go of me.
I'm really sorry that I couldn't tell you.
But I didn't tell you because I thought you wouldn't be my friend anymore.
Hey, Im Ju Gyeong. What do you see me as?
Did you even think of me as your best friend?
That's why I couldn't tell you even more.
But you told Su Jin.
You only told her and didn't tell me anything.
Did you think I wouldn't be your friend anymore if I saw your bare face?
No matter how thoughtless I look,
how could you see me as that kind of person?
Su Ah, I'm sorry.
I made all that fuss trying to get you a boyfriend.
You also didn't tell me you were dating Lee Su Ho.
Do I have to find out about your boyfriend through the bulletin board as your best friend?
I'm sorry, Su Ah.
What could have made her become like that?
It's not that she was made to be like that but that she chose to become like that.
How could she do something like that?
Kang Su Jin let go of our hands.
To her, you and I...
were just to this extent.
Let me see your face properly.
What's with your face that you had to tightly secure it...?
You'll become prettier if you take care of your skin.
Go to the dermatologist and get treated.
Drink a lot of water and eat vitamins.
Then that's it! Don't worry.
And... You have to tell me everything from the beginning to the end.
When did you start dating Lee Su Ho? Who confessed first? Does he treat you well?
Is Lee Su Ho, that psychopath, being short-tempered or anything like that?
He isn't.
What did you do well that you're smiling? You have to tell me everything from the beginning.
Everything, everything, everything! We're going to stay up all night, okay?
This... What's the meaning of it?
Hey, take it off. So dirty.
Was it not because you had feelings for me?
What are you saying?
I'm asking you for the last time.
Was it not because you thought of accepting me even a little bit?
- It wasn't.
- No! Give me evidence.
You really don't have feelings for me? Then step on me and go.
You have to think well.
I told you this is the last time—
I have no intention of staying as a friend like a fool
and having a heartbroken one-sided love like you.
Hey. Are you okay?
Are you crying?
It didn't look like you got hit that hard though.
Hyung! What should I do?
What do you mean?
Did you get rejected by Go Woon?
I really like her, but she says I'm not in her heart.
When I look at her, she's so pretty and I get so nervous.
How can I just be friends with her?
- That's true.
- If she comes to me, I have confidence that I'll treat her well.
- That's right.
- I didn't know a one-sided love would be this hard.
Who would've known?
But did you know?
That the person who has done everything he could do has no regrets either.
Because I properly confessed to her once and was rejected...
I think I now am able to sort out my feelings.
Oh! When did you guys start dating?
It hasn't been long.
They started dating since the field trip.
Since then? Wow, you seriously!
Hyeon Gyu's Patch would like to ask you a question.
When did you kiss for the first time?
At the field trip—
Why'd you ask that?
Seriously.
- Even I know that wasn't right.
- You guys all hate it if I even speak one word, right?
In order to have a flower bloom on the shaking tree branch,
the snow must have ceaselessly challenged itself.
Crunch, crunch. It must have knocked.
Flutter, flutter. It must have danced.
It must have slipped hundreds of times.
Look at the beauty of finally succeeding in blooming.
In spring, on the spot where it once burned,
The branch sprouts the most beautiful scar in the world.
On the spot where it once burned,
It sprouts the most beautiful scar in the world.
- How is it?
- It's nice.
- Tired?
- Yeah.
I couldn't sleep well. This won't do.
I'm going to the music room first and sleep. You should eat and then come.
How can I? Then you go on, I'll buy some things to eat.
No, it's okay...
♫ I just don't have the courage ♫
♫ I'm afraid it will be too much for you ♫
♫ I'm always anxious ♫
♫ I am loving you ♫
♫ Fall in you ♫
♫ I just found out ♫
♫ I am waiting for you ♫
♫ Fall in you ♫
♫ You are my destiny ♫
♫ The one person who will be my star ♫
♫ The one person whom I want to give my everything ♫
♫ You ♫
Who is it?
You woke up?
When did you come?
I woke up because of you.
My goodness, you must have been really tired.
Lee Su Ho's cousin.
I didn't mean to fool you.
Who was fooled?
You and Lee Su Ho are really obvious when you guys lie.
What? You knew then?
Why? What are you going to say?
You're similar with and without it.
What do they mean by they were deceived?
I can't understand.
- Thanks for the comfort.
- I'm saying both are ugly.
Are you teasing me?
But I heard that you were the one who took down my anonymous bulletin board video.
Thanks.
No problem.
Couple item. I'm so jealous.
I wish I also had a girlfriend.
Are you going on a date today? Where are you going?
Shall I tell you some of the popular places for dates?
I also know how to search it up.
The places that come up after searching are all advertisements.
There are a bunch of places that girls hate when you actually take them there.
This friend doesn't know a single thing about dating.
Is that so?
Where? Where? Let's see what you found.
Let's see.
- How is it?
- Uh...
- Not bad.
- Not bad at all.
- You tried.
- You tried, you tried.
- Wait, wait. What is this?
♫ I like you so much, what do I do? What do I do?
♫ You're so beautiful, what do I do? What do I do?
Hey!
Yo, cutie. You had a plan for everything. You're hard on the outside, but soft on the inside.
You're so soft.
- What do I do, what do I do?
- Be quiet.
- Our softy.
- Ju Gyeong!
What do I do, what do I do?
- Huh?
I'm taking her home today.
Sorry. I'll call you later.
♫ What to do with this? What to do, what to do?
♫ Shall we play with you? What to do, what to do?
♫ What to do, what to do?
Wow, this album picture is so cool. What do I do?
Wow, how long has it been since Crash's last song? What do I do?
It's unexpected of you who looks so adorable to like this kind of hardcore music.
- Please give us two corn dogs.
- That looks tasty.
Thank you.
Shall we see what's in Hye Min's backpack?
- It hurts a bit.
- It hurts?
- Will you hit her for me?
- I'll kill her for you.
What? Did they just drag someone from our school?
Im Ju, where are you going?
- Hey, Ju Gyeong! Im Ju Gyeong!
- I'm hungry.
- Please give me five corn dogs.
- Wait up. Let's go together.
Add five spicy rice cakes too.
More, more!
Left foot, left foot!
- When are you going home?
- Hey, quiet down.
Can you not talk to us when we're at an important moment?
Ah, seriously.
How much money do you have, Hye Min?
- What?
- You said you wouldn't look for me.
That you would let me go.
That's if you had dug up dirt on Im Ju Gyeong.
You didn't do anything. Is that not so?
Hey, Park Sae Mi!
- Im Ju Gyeong?
- It's our dumpling.
We were going to go see you anyway, but we meet like this.
Let go of Hye Min.
What if I don't want to?
Ju Hye Min, come here.
Where are you going?
Ju Gyeong!
You're dating Lee Su Ho and having Han Seo Jun by your side. You sure grew up a lot.
But I heard the video and picture got spread on the  bulletin board?
Your life got ruined. What to do? It's not like you can be reborn.
Hey!
This...
This crazy person, do you really want to die?!
In your own words, you guys are dead today.
You're low, waving around a weapon!
Hey, does your mom know you're going around like this?
Don't mess with my mom. Cham, cham, cham. Head!
You grew up a lot.
What are you carrying around?
Ah, that hurts!
Cunning bitch.
You're dead.
Left foot, right foot.
Okay!
This dumpling bitch.
Who are you trying to fool?
Arm, arm!
Hey, give it to me.
Wow, so you want to challenge me?
I'll accept that challenge. Bring it on, Lee Su Ho.
Su Ho, go go!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Bye, Hyeon Gyu.
Let go! Let go!
What are you guys doing? Get off!
Hey, let go.
Oi, Brother!
Which b**ches and jerk are messing with my Saebom friends?
Hey, I'll take care of this. You guys should go.
Thanks, Ju Gyeong.
From now on, never go with them.
If they try to take you, call the police right away, okay?
But I'm not afraid of Sae Mi anymore.
She wasn't much of anything earlier.
Why was I scared all this time?
I should have stood up to them sooner.
That's true. I should have also done it sooner.
I just got it today. Oh no!
Guys, sorry I couldn't protect you. It hurt a lot, right?
- Oh no.
- What do I do?
Do you want this? I usually buy two at a time.
Are you really giving this to me?
Thank you so much!
I'll buy you something delicious.
By the way, are you a Gelatin, too?
Yup, the third group of Gelatin. What about you?
- I'm the third group too.
- Really?
Awesome! Nice to know that!
Hey, did you succeed in getting the year-end concert tickets?
Yeah, section A standing.
- Awesome! I got section A, too.
- Really?
Yeah! We should go together. This is so great!
Enjoy the music.  By the way, what a shame to ruin this one...
The memory I never want to remember.
What's different is that I'm not alone now.
It's getting late.
To Girlfriend: Are you having fun?
Did you eat?
You're not answering your phone.
Should I come get you?
It's getting late.
You are a very tiring type.
Just eat. Why are you spying on my phone?
Let her let out her stress and have fun.
Why are you grilling her?
She'll call you on her way home.
This is an obsession. An obsession.
- I'm worried.
- I'm more worried about you.
I was just like that in the beginning of my relationship.
Every chance I got, I called and texted her.
In the end, I almost got dumped after a week.
- Su Ah told me I'm the tiring type.
- What?
- No matter how full of love you are, you should make her fret.
- Make her fret.
- So she doesn't get tired.
You should write this down.
You guys should go now. Leave quickly.
We have to finish this.
Su Ah, are you having fun?
I miss you so much!
I'll be right there to get you, Baby.
Hey, tiring... Not tiring.
Su Ho, I don't really know about relationships but what I think is—
Aren't you leaving?
I will try and eat very fast.
I should call Su Ho.
No.
Su Ah, Su Ah.
Hey, what do you want so late?
Send me a text right now. I think my phone is broken.
It's fine. It's totally fine!
If it's broken, how could you call me?
Seeing that I'm not getting any calls
- it's sending but I'm having problems receiving.
- You're so tiring.
Just go to bed. I'm going insane.
Hey, Yoo Tae Hoon.
Seriously!
Yoo Tae Hoon!
Is he still sleeping?
Girlfriend♡
I already cleaned the floor this morning. Stop it.
You're tired so I want to help out.
- Is there anything I can do?
- No.
Still. Should I sort these?
You're distracting me. Go home.
Mom, you know...
Just look under the chair.
- What?
- Just look as I said.
What is this?
Mom!
It looks like there are a lot of things to do like preparing for a performance test.
And it'll cost quite a bit to get all the materials.
How will you cover all that by working part-time?
Then are you giving me permission to pursue cosmetology?
Quit your work right away, too.
Since you've decided to do this, you should really work your butt off.
Become famous like that salad or Selena or something. Do you understand?
Mom!
What's wrong with you? Go away.
I'll really work hard. I love you, Mom.
- That tickles. It tickles.
- Thank you so much!
It tickles. Stop!
Im Ju Gyeong. Im Ju Gyeong!
- What.
- Why didn't you answer your phone yesterday? Why?!
I wanted to relieve some stress and have fun. Why are you grilling me?
You keep calling and texting. I want to be free now.
What do you mean? Are you saying we should break up?
You are really a tiring type.
What?
I'm not the tiring type.
- What do you think? You want to get on?
- Okay.
Don't get on. Don't go. Don't go!
Im Ju Gyeong. Im Ju Gyeong!
No!
What the? She did call.
What kind of dream is this?
Girlfriend♡
Hello?
What time did you get back home yesterday?
You said you'd call on your way back home. Why didn't you? I'm not trying to get an apology,
but if you're considerate of the person worrying, then you should've called.
I waited all night. But hearing your voice makes me want to see you.
So let's meet and talk right away. I was going to go see you.
You're a very tiring type.
Where are you?
My class is about to start. I'll call you when it's done.
What? Wait.
- Hello.
Thinking of a face's depth,
you should put more base where it's sticking out
and around delicate areas like mouth and eyes,
you should put just a little bit so the face doesn't look flat, right?
- Yes.
- Now, let's try it on the person next to you.
I received a call. Where is the guy?
Over there. He's totally out.
Gosh, thank you.
Wow. Jun Woo.
Wake up. Grapefruit! Grapefruit!
Did you call me?
- That's my girl.
- Oh my.
Is it not anymore? Since we broke up?
Oh la la?
How can I have you?
Oh dear...
Don't even think about running away and wait right there.
After one year, I'll make you my girl again.
You're killing me.
Buy One Get One free
I got them first.
Let go.
Okay, after you.
- What are you saying?
- Go ahead.
Where have I seen him before?
- Honey, eat this. Nose, nose, nose, mouth!
- C-Co!
Columbus Park! Stop right there!
Columbus, Columbus!
- Stop right there!
- Stop there! Get him!
This way. There you go.
I miss Hui Gyeong.
What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do? Get in somehow.
There you go. You weren't even going to last one day.
Sure, one year.
- Stop right there!
- What's going on?
Please get him! Please get him!
Darn it.
Oh my god...
Thank you.
Mom. Dad.
Hui Gyeong.
Grapefruit!
Oh, Lee Su Ho! You're pretty good.
You came?
- What are you doing on a weekend instead of going on a date?
- Ju Gyeong is busy.
- Are you upset that you couldn't meet her?
- What upset?
No matter how busy she is, why couldn't she meet you?
This face isn't the type that she would already get tired of so quickly, though.
Tired, my butt. Why did you come?
Just because. I was bored.
But why learn martial arts at a dojo? Learn from me.
- What do you know?
- What's the point of learning? Fighting is about senses.
Senses, my butt. It's about technique.
Did you see? This is the sense.
No matter how great your senses are, you won't ever be able to flip over a person who was taught.
- And if I do?
- If you do?
If I flip you over, what are you going to do?
Are you really bored?
The person who flips the other wins.
The loser will need to do everything the winner says.
- How does that sound?
- The pillars on your house are all going to get pulled out though.
Worry about your own house pillars.
Regardless of the rules, the winner is the one doing takedown for three seconds.
Deal.
One second, two seconds, two and one-fourth seconds, two and a half seconds.
You! You're letting your anger out on me, aren't you?
Three seconds.
See.  You should have let me win.
How is it? Do you want to learn from me?
I'm fine. What do you want me to do?
Tell me quickly.
♫ From far away, she is coming.
♫ How should I tell her about this trembling heart?
♫ From the start back then
♫ My heart was stolen and an incurable disease was given to me.
♫ I want to become a flowerpot. I always pray.
♫ I want to be a flowerpot that is sitting in your small window.
♫ Even if I can't say anything, even if I can't hope for anything
♫ As I receive your smile and your touches every so often
♫ I'll be able to endlessly see your sleeping face
- Here's the pizza you ordered.
- Thank you.
You will never see me playing a bet against you again.
- Were you hungry?
- Hey, with jujitsu and singing, how could I not become hungry?
By the way, your vocalization wasn't as good as back then.
What are you saying? It's become deeper and more manly.
That's what I'm saying. With that deep and manly voice, why aren't you singing?
What can I do now?
- It's not late yet.
- I don't want to.
I would like it if you sang again.
Se Yeon would have wanted that too.
If you won, what would you have said?
- Are you curious?
- Let's just hear it.
I was going to ask if it was okay for me to confess to Im Ju Gyeong.
I was going to get permission to do that.
Confession?
Yeah. I was going to get rejected and fold my feelings over for good.
Youth Pizza
But after hearing from him...
He also got his money taken by his boss and seemed to not have any money either.
If he had money, would he be in Korea?
He would have already flown over to another country.
But because he's been caught by the police, he'll pay for his sins now.
I thought if I caught him, I would be able to find all the money.
- I'm sorry, Honey.
- It's fine!
We should just think of it as all of this was our destiny and fate.
But at least, we avoided all those bullies who harassed Ju Gyeong and moved here.
And on top of that, Hui Gyeong met her other half. Don't you think so?
Yeah, Dad. If Ju Gyeong didn't go to Saebom High, I wouldn't have met my grapefruit.
But... When will our grapefruit wake up?
He keeps sleeping.
- Did you wait long?
- No.
Oh, I should charge my phone.
Did you order this? This looks tasty!
I ordered it so I could eat it.
- What's wrong? Are you angry at me?
- No.
- Then are you upset?
Do I look like someone who would get upset over something small?
Anybody can tell you're upset.
Oh, is that so?
Even with me here, you don't seem all that happy. Then I should leave.
Where are you going?
I shouldn't go?
Then what's wrong? Why are you upset?
Are you really not going to tell me?
You want to ask why? I feel like even after we started dating, we haven't gone on a proper date.
I prepared things after giving it some thought, but you say you're busy and I can't contact you all that much.
And Yoo Tae Hoon, that jerk,  told me that I'm the tiring type.
And Han Seo Jun asked me if he could confess to you.
My insides are all a mess right now. I'm getting all burnt up!
- Why?
- I love you.
I love you, Im Ju Gyeong.
If you do it suddenly, then...
Then?
I get nervous.
- How was the first lesson? Was it fun?
- Yeah.
Even if it was the beginner's class, everybody except me were like professionals.
Turns out I'm the only one who hasn't taken the written test.
So I'm going to try hard and succeed in one try.
After you finish the written test, shall we go somewhere?
- Where?
- Wherever you want.
Then shall we go see the beach?
Take the bus early in the morning and go to see the winter beach. How about it?
Okay. Let's do that.
Can't I really eat this?
- I ordered it for you to eat—
- So you were upset!
No, it was for us to eat it together. You and me. You eat and I eat.
I saw that you skipped your private tutoring again.
Even after getting reprimanded last time, you still haven't come to your senses?
Are you rebelling? I'm asking you what the problem is!
- Give me your phone.
- Why?
Whether it's because you're skipping out in order to fit in with people of low standards
or if it's because you're meeting some guy, I need to confirm for myself.
- Take out your phone.
- I don't want to.
Are you not going to take it out quickly?!
Have you gone crazy?!
- Did you bring the table out?
- Yeah.
- I'm so hungry.
- So hungry.
Dad, here's your rice.
- The soup!
- Bring it here.
Yup~
Grapefruit, come eat.
Thank you for the food.
- Eat a lot, Son-in-law Han.
- S-Son-in-law Han?
What Son-in-law Han? She said he's Grapefruit.
- Father, I'm not Grapefruit.
- Father?
You do seem like a grapefruit with your red cheeks.
I don't need to call you Teacher at home, right? Hm, Brother-in-law?
You're so dramatic.
Why did you say to break up because of me? Making me uncomfortable.
Starting today, it's the winter break and I'll soon change class years, so it's okay.
Ju Gyeong, I'm quite embarrassed.
What embarrassed? You're family now, Son-in-law Han.
Hui Gyeong, what happened to me?
What do you think happened to you?  You're now trapped by me.
Let me clean your eye.
Eat, eat. Eat, Grapefruit.
- Yes, I'll eat well.
- Eat, eat.
Wow, seriously.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Wow, she's here.
- Look at her.
Ju Gyeong, did you look at the bulletin board?
The bulletin board?
She didn't see it?
I didn't know she was that scary.  When everyone is talking about her...
I heard this from the girl's restroom.
Kang Su Jin from Grade 11 Class 5 is goosebumps inducing.
The person who released the video and picture of Im Ju Gyeong was Kang Su Jin.
The two were best friends but she exploded in jealousy over Lee Su Ho and Im Ju Gyeong dating and betrayed her.
I didn't make this up. I saw it firsthand, a different friend confronting Su Jin.
Isn't she like the villain in a drama?
It's not like she's a psychopath. Looks like she's the nation's betrayer.
- Wow, seriously.
- She went too far, really.
- Even so, to a friend?
- Because of a guy, she betrayed her friend?
She's seriously so-so. I didn't see her that way.
- Hey, isn't Im Ju Gyeong pitiful?
- That's true.
So the picture of Lee Su Ho and Im Ju Gyeong was also taken secretly by you?
Are you a stalker? Wow, you're so scary.
Kang Su Jin, how will you be able to hold your head high at school now?
Well, it's going to be hard for her, to be honest.
You think you destroyed Im Ju Gyeong, right?
The one who's destroyed is you.
She's totally a stalker.
Su Jin! Su Jin!
Where are you going?
Why are you running away?
You still have nothing to say to me?
You're not even a bit sorry?
Nope. I'm not sorry.
But still, I don't want us to be like this.
So I decided to hold out my hand for the last time,
because I don't want to regret anything later.
Su Jin, let's not be like this.
Do you think I'll hold on to your hand?
Did you believe that you and I could go back to how it was back then?
You're Ju Gyeong? Nice to meet you.
♫ I wouldn't know why I'm like this ♫
♫ You really drive me crazy ♫
♫ Even though I'm busy all day, when I have some time free ♫
♫ I wonder about you ♫
♫ I know it's not really playing hard to get, I have the unfamiliar feeling of swooning ♫
♫ I’m feeling good ♫
♫ Iike on the moon ♫
♫ I just think I can go anywhere ♫
♫ Now that we are a twosome ♫
♫ Call me maybe, you ♫
♫ Make me thrilled again. Love you ♫
The 30th National Cosmetology License Written Exam
♫ How far can we go tonight ♫
♫ Stay with me ♫
Did you not do well?
It's okay. You can do well next time.
I passed!
Good job.
They said I passed.
I guessed one and it was right.
You got lucky.
You're choking me.
Power of tiger, gush out! Roar!
Is this recyclable?
Whatever. Just throw it away.
Im Ju Gyeong
You must feel relieved now that your exam is done.
This is just the start.
I'm told that the written exam isn't even that hard.
Now I have to work hard for the performance exam.
It'll be harder to date now.
You have to study for your exams too.
Come to think of it, you haven't been studying lately.
My mind has been occupied by you.
Just a sec.
It's Han Seo Jun.
Hello?
Are you done with the exam?
That's why I'm answering.
What's up?
Can I see you right now?
Now?
I'm with Lee Su Ho. Should I come with him?
No. Just the two of us.
I have something to say.
Then today isn't a good time.
Remember my wish card?
I'll text you the place. Come there.
Hey, Han Seo Jun.
What the heck?
What did he say?
He has something to tell me and wants to see me,
but I'll just meet him some other time.
Go ahead.
- What?
- Go see him.
Han Seo Jun.
Why are you waiting outside when it's so cold?
Your nose is all red.
What is it that's so urgent?
Let's just go eat.
You're buying this.
You're using your wish card. You should've eaten something better than this.
You like this.
You're right. Honestly, I can eat this all week.
But what did you have to tell me?
You didn't call me to have me buy this, right?
I need a relationship advice.
What? Really?
But what do I know about relationships?
Just tell me for now. I don't know if I can be any help, though.
I have a crush on someone.
But I'm going to give up.
Why? Did you confess?
No.
You haven't even confessed, yet you're giving up?
She has a boyfriend.
Why did it have to be someone with a boyfriend?
Do you like her a lot?
Yes. A lot.
Oh no.
Then steal her.
Should I?
Who is it? Is she from our school?
I don't know. It's a secret.
No way.